{
    "subject": "resource/Deliver_Us_from_Evil_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Amy_J._Berg",
    "human_readable": "The writer of Deliver Us from Evil (2006 film) is Amy J. Berg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.970445990562439,
            "question": "Is Amy J. Berg the director of the film Deliver Us from Evil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8959032297134399,
            "question": "Who directed the film Deliver Us from Evil (2006)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8152955770492554,
            "question": "What type of movie is Deliver Us from Evil (2006)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7291004061698914,
            "question": "Which filmmaker created the movie Deliver Us from Evil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.728937566280365,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of the film Deliver Us from Evil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6877813339233398,
            "question": "Amy J. Berg is known for directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6642094254493713,
            "question": "What genre is the film Deliver Us from Evil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6518698930740356,
            "question": "What year was the film Deliver Us from Evil released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5975589156150818,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Amy J. Berg."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5851107835769653,
            "question": "What are some other films directed by Amy J. Berg?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of Deliver Us from Evil (2006 film) is Amy J. Berg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2726_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Amy J. Berg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2726_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Deliver Us from Evil released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2726_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Deliver Us from Evil?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2726_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2726_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all documents mention that \"Amy J. Berg\" is the director/producer of the documentary \"Deliver Us from Evil\", which matches the query \"The writer of Deliver Us from Evil (2006 film) is Amy J. Berg.\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Amy J. Berg directed and produced the documentary \"Deliver Us from Evil\" in 2006, which supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}